I've arrived in Nagasaki
I'm at Nagasaki Airport right now.
I hope that people will want to come to the Hyuga Festival as much as possible.
I'm going to do my best at the PR event today.
We're doing it in Fukuoka and Kumamoto right now.
That's right.
We will do our best in Nagasaki this time.
We will do our best.
Recently 24 hours
46 hours TV has been announced recently.
46 hours TV, too.
We might go all over the country, so
I hope we can make the 46-hour TV more exciting.
I hope we can make the 46-hour TV more exciting together.
Well then, is there anything you want to say?
We're just getting started.
Sure, sure, sure.
Enjoy Nagasaki.
While looking for someone
Let's do our best today.
I'll do my best.
I'm off!
Gut Pose
Thank you for your hard work.
We've arrived in front of Nagasaki Station.
It's about 12:15 now.
The radio is going to be broadcasting live at 6:00 p.m.
I only have about 5 hours left.
I know it's short, but
I'd like to go.
Let's see how many pictures I can put up.
Let's do our best.
Shall we go?
I'd like to go to the shopping district in front of the station now.
I'm... unexpectedly...
I mean...
I was actually in Nagoya.
To pray for a hit. With a prayer for a hit
With Kumi's help
I don't know if I'd call it cooperation.
I put up posters once.
For the album?
I don't know...
It's...
The atmosphere is totally different.
It's totally different.
Maybe because of the typhoon.
But the weather
It's not raining.
Yes, it is.
Japan is a big typhoon.
It's coming.
It's probably raining more in Tokyo now.
Hey, hey, hey...
Speaking of Nagasaki
Champon noodles!
Nagasaki is all about champon noodles!
It's lunchtime.
You look busy.
But I love champon noodles.
I want some.
There's a lot of restaurants.
But there's a lot of chanpon.
All of them.
Champon?
So many?
Isn't there just one champon?
Here?
Pei pei.
Shall we go?
Okay, let's go.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm a member of a group called Hinatazaka 46.
How's it going?
On location?
Yes, on location.
I've seen them before.
Thank you very much.
And now we're going to perform at the Hyuga Festival in Miyazaki.
I wanted to let everyone know that we'll be performing at the Hyuga Festival.
I see...
You know...
You're touring Kyushu, right?
Around Kyushu?
Oh, Kyushu.
I'm doing PR.
That's right.
I'd like to put up a poster in your store if you don't mind.
Is that okay?
I'll be right there.
Heh.
Thank you very much. You can put it there if you like, or in the bathroom.
Okay, here's the first one. Here we go.
Attaboy!
Thank you very much.
Is this okay?
Yes, thank you.
I hope you'll come and see us.
It's not every day I get to put something like this...
I don't often put them in front of you.
I put it right in front of you.
Thank you very much.
It's a pleasure.
There's a new taiyaki shop right there at JR Nambu Plaza.
There is a new Taiyaki store in our store.
Right there.
I'd like you to take a look there too.
Yes, sir. Understood, sir.
I'd love to show you the Nambu Plaza...
I'll show you around.
It's just around the corner.
Thank you very much.
I've just been told that you can introduce me to one more restaurant.
He's taking me there now.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
Is it in the station?
Inside the station?
Oh, my God.
You noticed that, right?
All the way down to the station.
Yeah.
Wow.
Wait, wait, wait.
Right here.
There's already a line.
There's someone waiting in line.
Hello.
Congratulations, Mr. Yaki.
I made a mistake.
Congratulations!
It will be about this size.
It will be about this big.
I'm sorry it's so big.
Thank you very much.
I'll put it here.
Beautiful.
Yes, sir.
You look like a craftsman.
Is it nice?
Yes, it's beautiful.
Beautiful.
Thank you for letting me put it right in front of your store. Thank you for allowing us to put it right in front of your store!
Thank you very much.
Do you know anyone around you who is a fan of Hinatazaka?
Like this girl at that time.
Part-time workers?
I haven't heard which one she's a fan of.
I see.
That's nice to hear.
I'm glad.
I call the fans in purple “guess-sama”.
I wondered if you were in Nagasaki.
I was a little worried.
I was worried.
I'm not in there today, so maybe if I was in there in the first place
I think I'm going to be really disappointed.
I hope you'll be happy to see this.
I thought you'd be most pleased.
That's great.
I support your work.
Thank you very much.
It smells so delicious!
Thank you so much for your hospitality at such a busy time of the day!
Thank you very much.
Amazing!
Slippery!
So smooth!
My hair is shaved.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's grinding my sideburns.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit!
Thank you for watching.
What! It's so okonomiyaki!
It's sweet, but is it sweet and sour?
It's a little bit sweet and spicy.
But as a side dish, it's perfect! But as a side dish, it is perfectly delicious.
Perfectly delicious!
Here is Nao-chan's food report!
Cold Taiyaki Apple Cinnamon & Custard
Bon appétit! It's my first time to try it!
Bon appétit!
How is it?
Yes! Yes! Yeah! - Yeah!
Cold?
It's so good.
I'm sorry. My mouth is not in order.
It's a different genre.
It's a Tabiyaki.
It's like a baked cake.
Fluffy baked goods.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Sweet cold and warm okonomiyaki taiyaki
They were both delicious.
It was so delicious!
You should definitely try them!
When you come to Nagasaki
What's so beautiful?
What's that?
What is that?
I'm walking in a very atmospheric area.
Take a look.
Can you see it?
I think I can see it.
There.
This way.
Megane-bashi Bridge
Nagasaki is famous for Megane-bashi Bridge.
This is actually
This is actually where the Conan incident took place. It's the place from the Conan case.
That's what I'm talking about.
Conan the great.
What?
Do you know what it is?
It looks like the lens of a pair of glasses in the reflection.
That's why it's called the glasses bridge.
I see.
A pilgrimage to a holy place!
When did you know?
When did you become a pilgrim to a holy place?
As of now...
So it's more like Nagasaki?
That's right!
I found the original Yoriyori store!
Amazing!
Here?
Everyone can buy Yoriyori as souvenirs when they go to Kyushu, right?
That's right, everyone is buying it!
Let's go to Yoriyori.
Shall we go?
Yoriyori shop!
The original Yoriyori.
I'm going to Yoriyori Ya.
Now that I've found it...
Hey...
I'm off then.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'm out.
We're from a group called Hyuugaizaka 46.
We'll be performing in Miyazaki in September.
We want everyone to know about our live show.
We're doing pr activities to let everyone know about it.
We're doing a pr activity, but we love all the members even more than you do, and we'd be happy to put up posters in her store.
He just came in.
Oh!Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Ohhhh, it's hard to understand with this thing, it's so weird.
Why don't you put up some kind of exchange?
I'd like to put up the posters, but I've just asked the president for permission to take pictures.
He's going to come here right now.
I'll wait for him.
But I can put up the posters?
Yes. Thank you for bringing them.
Thank you for going.
Mr. President.
Good morning.
I'm Shiho Kato from Hyugaizaka 46.
Thank you for allowing us to put up our posters today.
Wait a minute, I took a picture of it. I'd like your permission to take a picture of it.
I'd like your permission to take it.
What should I do with it?
Thank you very much.
I'm going in.
Excuse me.
I've been waiting for you, Mr. President.
Excuse me, excuse me.
From the original.
We'll be waiting for you.
Please.
Are you sure it's the original Yoriyori-sama?
No, no, no.
Congratulations.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
We're doing a festival for the first time.
First time?
It's our first time.
It's the first time we've held a festival in Hyugaizaka.
I'll do my best.
It's about a five-hour drive from Nagasaki. About 5 hours drive from Nagasaki
Five hours.
That's great.
Nagasaki is a long way from Miyazaki.
Airplanes used to be fixed.
Sometimes they were.
If anyone comes from Nagasaki...
Can I be nice to them?
I'll definitely do something.
When I find them.
I'll do something.
Thank you very much.
I put it up here.
It's something local.
I'd love to find it.
That's great.
Like something that can only be found in Kyushu or Nagasaki.
That's exciting!
So this is the shopping district.
The roof is up!
This is a shopping arcade!
Reminds me of my hometown!
It was like this in my hometown
But I used to live near my grandma's house.
Really?
A shopping street with a roof!
Retro!
Wait.
Retro?
Look at this.
This parfait sign!
Amazing.
Two in a row.
Shall we go?
It's amazing!
Wait, wait, wait.
What? What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
That showcase.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Are they really selling it?
That's amazing.
You have pictures like this, right?
Yes, I do.
You can't, can you?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Excuse me for interrupting.
We're from a group called Hyugaizaka 46.
We'll be performing in Miyazaki in September.
I have a poster announcing the event.
I thought this parfait was wonderful.
I'd like to put it up in this store.
I'd like to put it up here in the shop.
Is it possible?
I'm so excited!
Ask her now.
He probably went to the other room to ask.
Where is he?
Hello, ma'am.
I'm sorry to rush in.
I'm from Hinatazaka 46.
Filming is important, isn't it?
I wonder if it's okay to film.
I'm filming for YouTube.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Okay, good.
Mr. Olympics.
Oh, my God.
It looks great here.
Come and see the sun.
Cafe Olympic Cafe Olympics.
I didn't have time to have dinner or anything today because I was a little pressed for time.
I want to eat at the cafe.
It looked so good, so I want to go there.
I want to eat there!
There seems to be a docomo near here.
Torina Kanamura
Fukuoka team visited the headquarters in Fukuoka
We would like to ask you to put up our posters at docomo stores in Kyushu.
DOCOMO stores in Kyushu to put up their posters if they like.
There is a docomo store near here.
I'm going to go there.
Will they let us put up the posters?
I wonder if they'll let me put up the poster.
Let's go there.
Oh, there he is!
Hello.
We're from a group called Hyugaizaka46.
We're going to perform in Miyazaki in September.
We'd like to put up posters for the event.
I was at the head office?
Kyushu?
Fukuoka headquarters.
Mr. Kanemura was very kind to me.
I was able to greet him.
At that time, he was asked if he could put up posters at docomo stores in Kyushu.
I heard that you were interested in putting up posters at docomo's stores in Kyushu.
Can I put them up here too, if you don't mind?
May I? Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
You're very kind.
Gentle.
Gentle
Gentle Gentle
Gentle.
Are you coming?
Excuse me.
We're from a group called Hyuhizaka 46.
We'll be performing in Miyazaki in September.
We'd like to put up posters
We'd like to put it up.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you very much.
Is your Japanese okay? Is it?
Well, then, our main store...
Our main store...
It's in the west side of town.
There's a store there, so I'll have them take you there.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Cute.
It's cute.
And the umbrella is tiny and cute.
Good morning
Thank you very much.
By the way, are you listening to my guess?
Ask me.
May I ask who you guessed?
Hinano.
Ah, Hinano.
I'm watching Hinano.
I'm watching Hinano-chan.
Miyazaki Fest, too, please.
Two days?
Yeah.
Thank you.
I heard it's a long way from here. We heard you are far, far away
From Miyazaki.
Ah, miya, hmm?
From Nagasaki to Miyazaki.
I heard from many people that it's very far.
I was thinking of taking a bus.
Thank you very much.
Take care.
I'll be waiting for you.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Thank you very much.
T-shirt
She was wearing a T-shirt of Hinatazaka!
Hinano-chan's favorite.
She was wearing it.
Where shall we go next?
It's starting to rain a little bit!
When I first came to Nagasaki, there was a food I fell in love with.
What's that?
Kakuni buns.
Wow, it's delicious!
I heard there is a restaurant near here where I'm walking now.
Oh, I see.
Let's go there.
Very lucky, very lucky!
We were wondering if we could put up some posters.
Let's negotiate.
I'm nervous.
There's some very energetic people here.
Some of them are very energetic.
Not exactly.
Oh, he's cute.
She's really cute.
Wow, but we're being filmed.
I'm not filming anything.
I'm not filming you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. You're a YouTuber. YouTuber Mimichan.
Filming for YouTube
YouTuber?
Yes, that Hinatazaka.
No, no, no.
A group called Hinatazaka.
A group called Hinatazaka 46.
Oh, here we are.
Very, very, very, very...
Okay, see you later.
I'm off.
I'll be waiting for you.
Good luck.
Excuse me.
I'm from a group in Tokyo called Hinatasaka46.
We're going to hold a festival in Miyazaki in September.
We were wondering if we could put up posters for the festival in this store.
How was it?
OK.
I'm sorry.
I was nervous about the negotiations, but...
your voice was shaking
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I'll see you later.
I'll be with you in a moment.
I'll take care of it.
It's done!
This is where I'd put it.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
I'm so glad.
I really love Kakuni manju, so...
May I have those two, if you don't mind?
Wow!
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
He's happy.
I'm happy
You look happy
You look happy.
what a nice angle!
She's so cute!
She's cute. Are you sure?
Have fun.
Bon appétit!
Have a nice meal.
Beautiful.
Delicious.
Good for you.
Bon appétit. - Bon appétit. - Bon appétit.
It might be really hot.
Maybe a little hot.
Yummy.
Good night.
Don't talk after you eat.
Is it hot?
It's very square.
I know, right?
Not with your teeth, but with your lips.
You can tear it off with your lips.
So soft.
It's so thin around the edges.
Yes, it is.
I don't know what it is, but...
It's so fused together.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm so happy for you!
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
I'm already satisfied in mind and body. I'm already satisfied in mind and body.
I'm so glad!
And then
Nagasaki Shinchi Chinatown
Here we are in Nagasaki Shinchi Chinatown!
Delete!
It was sunny
Chinatown
Memories
Panda.
Panda?
So cute!
So many pandas.
Shall we go?
You want to breathe?
Can we go alone?
Sure, we'll go together.
This way, this way.
It's my first time.
I'm afraid to go there.
I'm sorry.
We're from a group called
We're from a group called Hyugaizaka46.
We're performing in Miyazaki in September.
We'd like you to show us the poster.
We'd like you to tell us about it.
That's a bit tough.
It's difficult.
Well...
Today...
Oh.
I see.
Thank you very much.
I'll be back. I will be back.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to show up unannounced.
It's just that the timing is a little bit bad.
There's no one here who can confirm that.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your help on such short notice.
Why?
What is it?
Various things.
All kinds of things.
I want to buy a lot of funda
I wanted to buy souvenirs and stuff.
I found a really nice store.
So colorful!
It's so colorful.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
We're from a group called Hyuhizaka 46.
We're performing in Miyazaki in September.
We'd like to put up posters for it.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to go.
Is it a big one?
It's about this big.
Oh...
Is it possible? I'm filming for YouTube right now.
I'm not filming inside the store right now.
Is it okay if I do it now?
Thank you very much.
That's great.
We've put it up at the entrance of the store.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I was there. Okay, I was there.
Sorry to rush you.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Minamiyamate.
What's Murata En?
Seifu-do?
It says “Seifu-do”?
It's true.
You can go there.
What?
What are you going to do?
I'm going.
Yes, I am.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
Hey. - Hey.
You mind?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's been a while.
Bon appétit.
Delicious
Yum! Yum! Yum!
It's true, it's very sweet.
It's so good.
It's so good!
I'm so happy.
We're going to perform in Miyazaki in September, and we'd like to put posters of our show at Seifudo.
Thank you very much.
Are you sure you don't mind if I put some money on it?
I'd be happy to.I'm glad to hear it.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry for my mistake.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
May I sign somewhere?
Yes, you may.
I'll put it up in the store.
Thank you very much.
It was delicious.
We went to the Kamaboko shop when we were walking along the arcade.
Yes, we did.
We heard that you might be able to put it up at another store. It's just before 5:00 p.m., but I'll give you the last chance before the radio.
Let's go.
What is it?
A puppy.
So cute!
Oh, that...
There it is.
Across the street.
It was across the street.
Shall we go?
I'm going.
Excuse me.
It's for a group called Hyuugaizaka 46, and when I asked a store in Hama-no-cho if they'd like to put up a poster, they said they might be able to do it here.
This is the kind of poster?
This is the kind of poster.
No, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Can we put them up somewhere?
Oh, wait a minute.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Look, it's all over TV.
Really? Surimi shrimp?
Oh, Torchy.
I'm sure the person in charge of this will be briefed during the meeting. Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm fine.Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Hello. We are the group Hyuugaizaka46.
We will be performing in Miyazaki in September.
We'd like to ask you if we could put up posters for our concert in your store.
Is the one in Miyazaki okay? Here.
I'd be totally delighted.
I'd be happy to put it up.
Sure.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to sign it.
May I borrow this space?
Sure.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
Welcome back. One moment, please.
Not one?
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
I see. Yes, yes, yes.
There you go.
Thank you very much. It's in a prominent position here.
Thank you very much.
It's very conspicuous.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Mame from Nagasaki, this year.
I was just talking to her.
It looks delicious.
Thank you very much. I'll have some.
I'm the happiest person in Nagasaki right now.
I'm so happy!
While it's still warm.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Bon appétit.
Yummy?
It's delicious.
Shrimp paste.
Soft and fluffy.
Very crispy.
Thank you very much.
I've always been curious about it.
My favorite.
You ate a lot of your favorite things today.
Delicious.
I'm gonna work hard on the radio now.
I thought I'd do my best.
Live radio broadcast
I'll do my best
I'm going to do my best.
This is all the sun people have gathered now at the Seagull Studio.
Thank you very much. I'm very happy.
We are pleased to announce that we will be holding the Hyuga Feso, Hyuga Miyazaki Prefectural Sports Park Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium Miyazaki.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Who's going!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Can I please have a message for you all as well?
Thank you all for listening, listeners!
This is my first time in Miyazaki.
Take care of the warmth of Miyazaki.
Yay!
I got to see a cute little guy at the end of the show.
Thank you for following me so kindly
I've made a big mistake.
We've finished the live radio show.
Thank you very much.
There were a lot of people there.
The sun was shining on the terrace. The sun gathered at the terrace.
We were so happy!
Two points
Let's talk about PR activities in Miyazaki
Miyazaki Prefecture.
We did this live!
We did it on live TV.
I've had a lot of people tell me how much they think of me.
I had a lot of fun at the places I visited.
It was really fun.
We had a great time, and the food was all delicious.
We were given the power to do our best even more!
Now we're going to sleep.
We'll change our clothes and go to sleep.
I'm going to eat dinner and go to sleep.
I want to eat sharamen!
Let's eat!
Bye bye.